This program is organized into four courses;
该方案分为四个课程 ;
foundations, object-oriented programming, memory management and concurrency.
基础 面向对象编程 内存管理和并行
In the foundations course,
在地基上
you'll learn about C plus plus syntax and how to compile and run C plus plus programs.
您将了解 C + 语法以及如何编译和运行 C + + 程序
You'll also learn about the input and output features of the language,
您还会了解语言的输入和输出功能
as well as how to declare and initialize variables,
以及如何声明和初始化变量
structure your code using conditionals and loops,
使用条件和循环来构造代码
and organize your code using functions.
并组织您的代码使用功能
In the object oriented-programming course,
在面向对象编程过程中
you'll learn how to further organize your code into classes,
你会学习如何进一步把你的代码组织成班级
and you'll learn how to expose interfaces to those classes to other users.
并且您将了解如何向其他用户公开这些类的接口
You'll also learn how to declare certain interfaces to be
您还将学习如何将某些接口声明为
public and certain to be private using access modifiers.
使用访问修饰符的公共和特定于私有
You'll cover the core concepts of
您将涵盖以下核心概念 :
object-oriented programming generally including encapsulation,
面向对象程序设计 一般包括封装
abstraction, inheritance and polymorphism,
抽象 继承和多态性
and you'll learn how to implement
你会学会如何实施
those features using the C plus plus programming language.
这些功能使用 C + + 编程语言
You'll close this course by learning about generic programming and how to
您将通过了解通用编程以及如何
use C plus plus templates to make your code more generic.
使用 C + + 模板使您的代码更通用
In the next course,
在接下来的课程中
you'll learn about memory management.
您将了解内存管理
Memory is incredibly important to the C plus plus programming language.
记忆对 C + + 编程语言非常重要
You'll learn how to pass around both references and pointers,
你会学会如何通过引用和指针
and you'll learn about the differences between memory on
你会了解记忆之间的差异
the stack and memory allocated from the heap.
从堆分配的堆栈和内存
You'll also learn how to take advantage of scope and use the resource acquisition
您还将学习如何利用范围和使用资源获取
is initialization paradigm in order to keep track of memory that's used by your program.
是初始化范例 以便跟踪程序所使用的内存
You'll close this course by learning about smart pointers,
您将通过了解智能指针来关闭此课程
which are the best way to keep track of pointers and
这是跟踪指针的最好方法
dynamically allocated memory in modern C plus plus.
在现代 C + +中动态分配内存
The final course is concurrency.
最后的课程是并行的
In this course, you'll learn how to organize your code using both processes and threads,
在此课程中 您将学习如何使用流程和线程来组织代码
and you'll learn how to synchronize and communicate between threads.
然后学习如何在线程之间进行同步和通信
In particular, you'll learn about features of the C plus plus programming language that
尤其是 您将了解 C + + 编程语言的特点
support concurrent multi-threaded programming including promises and futures,
支持并发多线程编程 包括承诺和期货
and mutexes, and locks.
还有互斥锁
By the time you're done with all four of these courses,
当你完成所有四种课程的时候
you will be a terrific C plus plus developer.
你会是个了不起的 C + 开发商